In this course, you're going to be
talking a lot, a LOT about relationships.
No, not that kind of relationship, sorry.
We're going to be talking about
relationships between quantities.
Yeah, like that.
A graph is one way to show a
relationship between two quantities.
In this case, the graph shows that the
elevation of a skier goes down over time.
In other words, as the quantity "time"
increases, the quantity "elevation"
decreases.
The two quantities here have specific names.
The elevation of the skier depends on
the time, so elevation in this situation
is called the dependent quantity.
And time is called the independent
quantity.
This line represents a trip down
a ski slope.
But the line also has something called slope.
Do you remember what slope is?
How would you describe the slope of this
line?